<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ishan</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ishan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Ishan Chag</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 10:49:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My First Project</title>
      <link>/posts/myfirstproject/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 10:49:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/myfirstproject/</guid>
      <description>This week I have completed my first publicly viewable web design project You can view it here. This project was a test to see how easy and intuitive Google Sites was being a piece of free software. The experiment was extremely interesting and I found Google Sites to be a neat piece of software. Highlight features include: embed code feature (useful for iframes and other HTML items), branding features (auto colour schemes and handling of header and footer) and the free hosting - Google Sites hosts your website, even with a custom domain, free of charge with a few simple changes in the DNS records.</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This week I have completed my first publicly viewable web design project&lt;/strong&gt;
You can view it &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.apexracing.uk&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. This project was a test to see how easy and intuitive Google Sites was being a piece of free software. The experiment was extremely interesting and I found Google Sites to be a neat piece of software. Highlight features include: embed code feature (useful for iframes and other HTML items), branding features (auto colour schemes and handling of header and footer) and the free hosting - Google Sites hosts your website, even with a custom domain, free of charge with a few simple changes in the DNS records. I would highly recommend this for people starting out in Web Development because of how it nicely combined simplicity and flexibility all in a free web-based program.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to my site</title>
      <link>/posts/welcometomysight/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 10:11:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/welcometomysight/</guid>
      <description>Hi, welcome to my site. My name is Ishan Chag and I am an aspiring web developer. More site changes coming in the future. On this site I will link and show my projects and talk about my experience using new software technologies.</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hi, welcome to my site.&lt;/strong&gt; My name is Ishan Chag and I am an aspiring web developer. More site changes coming in the future. On this site I will link and show my projects and talk about my experience using new software technologies.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
